声明: 本字幕由YYeTs美剧字幕组原创翻译制作
欢迎访问官方论坛  www.YYeTs.net 在线观看 剧情讨论 学习交流
=====本字幕由以下成员荣誉制作 感谢他们的无私奉献======
翻译：Requiem校对：扣扣
后期：阿胜 双语制作：tamama788
========== 字幕总监制：七色九天 ==========
前情提要
Previously on Lost
我想我没事
I think I'm all right.
我说过我会照顾你
I told you I'd take care of you.
-谢谢  Charlie  -不用客气
-Thanks Charlie  -You are quite welcome
Sayid
这岛上不光只有我们
We're not alone.
有人看到Ethan了吗?
Has anyone seen Ethan?
恩  恩  他去海滩了
Yeah  Yeah  He took off on the path to the beach
-Charlie去哪儿了?  -他去找Claire了
-Where's Charlie?  -He went after Claire.
脚印  这里到处都是三种不同的脚印
Footprints, three distinct sets, all over the place.
我看他们被劫走了
I think they've been taken.
Claire
他们想要的就是Claire
All they wanted was Claire.
Walt
嘿  Michael  看到Claire的包了吗?
Hey Michael  Have you seen Claire's bags?
-看到我儿子了吗?  -看到她的包了吗?
-Have you seen my son?  -Have you seen her bags?
她的行李, 没拿到这来
Her luggage. It's not been brought back here.
看来没人知道到哪儿去了
No one seems to know what's happened to it.
不好意思 兄弟 我不知道  我在找Walt
Sorry, man. I don't know. I'm just looking for Walt.
是这样 不好意思  我没看到他
Oh. Got it. Sorry. I've not seen him.
Jack 你在那边看到我儿子了吗?
Hey, Jack. You seen my boy when you were out there?
没有  他当时在山洞那边
No. He was at the caves.
恩  他遛狗去了
Yeah, he took his dog for a walk.
我和他说别往远处走...
Told him to stay close as usual.
你10岁的时候听你老爸的话  是吧
You listened to your old man when you were ten,right?
呃  恩
Uh, yeah.
恩  我听  可能有点太听话了
I listened. Maybe a little too well.
老兄  新一轮的比赛要开始了
Yo,dudes,got a new tourney lined up.
看谁能赢得最后一支除臭棒
We're playing for the last of the deodorant sticks.
打会儿高尔夫不?
You dawgs up for some golf?
我要去找我孩子
I gotta go find my kid.
如果看到了Walt
Hey,if Walt shows up,
告诉他在这儿等我回来
tell him to stay right here until I get back.
一定
You got it.
-Walt  -看起来他厌烦了  是吧
-Walt!  -He seems to hate it, doesn't he?
-什么  -当一名父亲
-What?  -Being a dad.
不  只是...
No, it's just...
-一刻不得闲呐  -Walt
-a lot of hard work.  -Walt
Walt
不  是他厌烦了
Nah, he hates it.
Walt
就是这个了
This is the one.
这个肯定就是我宝宝的婴儿床了
This is definitely my baby's crib.
漂亮啊
Beautiful.
放在我们将要住的小通道里会很棒
It'll look great in the alley we'll be living in.
这要三个月的租金那
This is three months' rent.
什么  不是三个...
What? It's not three...
你难道不想孩子过的好吗?
Look, don't you want the best for this kid?
我知道你很激动  但Michael我们买不起
I know you're excited, but Michael we can't afford this.
我们的宝宝在这婴儿床上
Our baby in this crib.
拜托  那会是个开心的小家伙
Come on. That's a happy kid.
我和Andy谈了
Hey I talked to Andy.
他说他能给我找点活干
He said he can throw some work my way.
建筑吗?  那你的艺术怎么办呢?
Construction? What about your art?
不  不  不
No. No. No.
我不会放弃  只是想放下一段时间
I'm not giving it up. I'm just gonna take a break
到你完成了法学院的学业再说
until you finish law school.
通过律师考试  被某不错的法律公司高薪聘用
Pass the bar, get hired by some fancy-ass, high-paying law firm.
有人把一切都计划好了
Somebody's got it all figured.
恩  我最终还会回去画画
Yeah,I'll get back to painting eventually.
与此同时  你将会习以为常的...
Meanwhile, you can support me and Walt...
支持我和Walt
in the manner to which we'll soon become accustomed.
Walt  是吗?
"Walt" huh?
我想喜欢这样
I'd like to do that, you know.
让他随我父亲的名字
Name him after my dad.
Walter
Walter Lloyd
Lloyd
好吧  就因为这你才不愿嫁给我
Oh, all right. That's why you won't marry me.
而不是因为你认为婚姻生活枯燥无味
It's not that marriage is too prosaic.
你只是想要他随你姓
You want him to have your last name.
你还想不想让我同意Walter了
Hey, you want me to agree to "Walter," or what?
天  我逊毙了
Man, I suck.
你能做的更好
You can do better than that.
你别逼他就好
You might wanna take it easy on him.
看到这个结了吗  Walt?
See this knot, Walt?
你就瞄准它  就瞄这儿
I want you to aim for it. Right here.
全神贯注  好吗?
Focus on it. All right?
用你心灵之眼来想象一下
Picture it in your mind's eye.
你知道什么是心灵之眼吧
You know what that is, right? the mind's eye?
就象是在脑袋里形成一幅画
Like a picture in your head.
说的对  再来一次  但要看到才行
That's Right.Now do it again, but see it.
在你投出去之前要先看到
See it before you do it.
看到那条轨迹
Visualize the path.
看到那轨迹
See it.
-哇噢  -好唉
-Whoa.  -Yes!
我就知道你有那潜质  Walt
I knew you had it in you, Walt
怪了  我真的...
It was weird. I actually saw it
在我心里看到了  象是真的一样
in my mind or something, like it was real.
谁说不是呢
Who's to say it wasn't?
这是怎么回事
Hey! What the hell is going on?
-给我  -但是我...
-Gimme that.  -But I...
带Vincent回营地去
Take Vincent and go back to camp.
-可Locke先生在...  -快  小子
-But Mr. Locke was...  -Now, little man.
你给我孩子一把刀?
You gave my boy a knife?
你该先看看...
You should've seen...
用不着你告诉我该看什么  老兄
Don't tell me what I should've seen, man.
这要是在家里  我就去报案抓你了
If we were back home, I'd call the police on your ass!
教唆孩子从他老爸那溜走
Encouraging a kid to sneak away from his parent.
给他这样的一把刀
Giving him a knife like this?
Walt自己能分辨是非
Walt knows his own mind.
别说得像你了解他似的!
Don't talk to me about my son like you know him!
你冷静一下吧
You really need to calm down.
你如果继续让我儿子和我作对
You keep playing my son against me
我就会...
and I'm gonna have a...
人家说让你冷静
The man said "calm down"
-你算哪根葱 他的走狗吗?  -冷静 冷静 冷静
-What are you, his attack dog?  -Easy easy easy
是你拿把刀挥来挥去的
You are the one who was waving the knife around.
他只是不想让你伤到人
He was just trying to make sure you didn't hurt someone.
Michael  我知道...
Michael, I know...
你和你儿子之间沟通困难
it's been difficult to bond with your son.
你知道他为什么喜欢跟我在一起吗?
You know why he's formed an attached to me?
因为我把他当作大人来看待
Because I treat him like an adult.
可你还是把他当成孩子
and you still treat him like a boy.
他10岁
He's ten years old.
他所经历的要比有些人一辈子经历的还要多
He's been through more than most people in their entire lifetime.
你没和他在一起多久所以你不知道
You haven't spent enough time with him to see it
但他与众不同
but he's different.
你说什么
What did you say?
这不是家里  Michael
And we're not back home, Michael
只要我们在这儿
As long as we're here
我觉得你该让他认识到他的潜能
I think Walt should be allowed to realize his potential.
离我儿子...
You stay away from my son...
和我远点儿
and me.
你不能带走他
You're not taking him.
不能带走我儿子
You're not taking my son.
你想走可以走  但Walt要留下
You can go if you want to, but Walt stays with me.
我是想和你商量一下
I'm trying to have a discussion with you.
你说的是要去阿姆斯特丹...
You're talking about going to Amsterdam...
只有你和他  这怎么能算是商量呢?
just you and him. How is that a discussion?
是工作的机会  Michael  那是工作地点
It's an offer, Michael, and that's where the job is.
你说过你快乐啊
You said you were happy.
那"法律诊所挺适合我"又算作什么?
What about the legal clinic being a good fit?
-你说过的  -千载难逢的机会啊
-You said that.  -This is a huge opportunity.
你知道我一直期盼做国际法
YOu know I've always wanted to do International Law.
我是该在这儿替你高兴吗?
Am I supposed to be happy for you over here?
为你那"千载难逢的机会"高兴吗?
for your huge opportunity?
我们谈论过要分开一段时间
We've talked about taking some time apart.
宝贝儿  我以为那是...
Look, babe, I thought that was...
我们谈论过很多事
Hey, we said a lot of things.
你说你想在一条船上住
You said you wanted to live on a boat.
我还是爱你的
I still love you.
这你知道  可我...
You know I do, but I...
Michael  这么短时间里我们经历的太多了
Michael  we've been through so much in such a short time.
宝贝儿  我们有分歧  可那正常啊
Babe, we got problems. That's what people have.
你想去咨询吗?
You wanna go to counseling?
我没问题  我们走吧
I'm down with that. Let's go.
好吗
All right?
噢  天
Oh, man
你已经接受了  是吧?
You already took it, didn't you?
那份工作
The job.
恩  是的
Yeah, I did.
你已经几个月没工作了
You haven't worked in months.
建筑业在冬季很低靡
Construction slows in the winter.
-这我和你说过  -我可以给他一切
-I already told you.  -I can provide for him
我会给他他所需要的一切
I'll give him everything he needs.
除了他老爸  你不能带走他  不能
Except for his dad.He's not going with you! No!
你真要为这事和我争吵吗?
You wanna argue with me about this?
奶奶的  说对了  这种事法律上是站不住脚的
Hell.Yes. There are laws against this kinda thing.
我们还没结婚  Michael
We're not married, Michael.
我是他母亲并且有稳定的工作
I'm his mother, and I'm steadily employed.
你说法庭会把他判给谁
Who do you think the court's gonna side with?
这并不是永远说再见
This is not goodbye forever.
我只是...
I just...
我需要些时间
I need some time.
你没事吧
Are you all right?
恩  我没事
Nah  I'm okay.
谢了
Thanks.
还是不知道怎么和他沟通
I just don't know how to talk to him.
怎么让他...
How to get him to...
让他知道我站在他那一边
you know, understand I'm on his side.
Locke说我不该再把他当作孩子看了
Locke says I should stop treating him like a child.
我错过了他整个的童年  所以...
I missed his whole childhood, so...
不能这样
It just can't happen.
什么?
What?
他不能在这儿长大
He can't grow up here.
He can't grow in this place.
当我认识到这些方程式是些坐标...
Once I realized these equations were coordinates...
经纬度...
latitude and longitude...
我猜想那法国女人是想要确定这岛的方位
I assumed the french woman was trying to determine the location of the island.
可并未完成
But it was incomplete
她作的记号七零八碎
her notations fragmented
除了那首鱼谣
Except for the fish song.
恩那
Mm-hmm.
什么
The what?
当我把纸象这样放着的时候
When I lay the pages down like this
我发现这不是表明这座岛的方位
I realized it wasn't showing the location of the island.
我看是这岛上的方位  特指这里
I think it's a location on the island.Specifically, here.
那相对于三角形来说我们的位置在哪儿?
So where are we in relation to the triangle?
这地图比例不准  所以我也不知道
Well, the map is hardly at scale,so I don't know.
我们甚至都不确定这是否是这座岛的地图 对吧?
We're not even sure it's a map of this island, are we?
对  不知道
We're not.no.
但这也许是发送器发出求救信号和它电源的地方
This may be the transmitter sending out her distress call,and its power source.
在谈什么呢?
What are we talking about doing now?
在想方设法被追捕 被森林里的东西干掉吗?
loking for another excuse to get chased down and killed by whatever lives in the jungle?
伙计们  我们不能再这样下去了...
Guys, we can't keep doing this.
建造水过滤系统和打高尔夫
Building water filtration systems,and playing golf.
把这当成温暖的家  我们要离开这座岛
making a sweet home here. We need to get off this island!
你以为谁想这样吗?
You think any of us wanna be here?
不  可我看现在谁都没有我回家的愿望那么强烈
No. But I don't think anyone wants to get off as much as I do right now.
那你有什么好办法吗?
So, are you suggesting something?
恩
Yeah.
我们造一个木筏
We build a raft.
木筏
A raft?
别用那种语气跟我说话  老兄
Don't say it like that, man
我们要有点乐观精神  知道吗?
We need a little optimism here,okay?
我们要做点事情  因为说实话
And we gotta do something, 'cause,let's be honest,
没人会来了
no one's coming.
我们在机舱里拿的那些座位...就可以漂着
Those seats we took off the fuselage, they float.
我们还有一把斧头
And we got an axe.
还有一大片树林  竹子
And a whole bunch of trees, bamboo.
我们做得到的
We can do this.
在惊涛骇浪中生存的机会...
The chances of surviving the rough waters...
找到一条航线的几率...
The odds of finding a shipping lane...
我还严重晕船
And I get really seasick.
好极了  留在这吧
You know what? Great. Stay here.
度过今生  祝你们好运吧
Grow old, good luck to you.
但我要这么做  我儿子和我要离开这儿
But I'm doing this. My son and I are leaving.
谁要帮我们造的话会得到上帝的保佑
Anybody that wants to help us build,  God bless you.
嘿  Walt
Hey, Walt.
嘿  走
Hey, come on.
我需要你帮点忙
I need your help with something.
我在做事
I'm doing stuff.
你在看西班牙文的漫画 你又不懂西班牙文
You're reading comics in Spanish, and you don't read Spanish, man.
我喜欢这些画
I like the pictures.
你喜欢艺术  是吧
You like the art, huh?
是吧
I guess so.
我像你那么大的时候...也许比你还大点...
You know, when I was your age, I don't know, maybe a little older,
我总是映描漫画
I traced comics.
自学透视画法  你知道是什么吗
Taught myself about perspective.You know what that is?
透视画法
Perspective?
嘿
Hey.
我说要你帮忙  走
I said I need your help. Let's go.
为什么我要去
Why do I have to come?
因为我知道我一眼盯不住你就会怎样
Because I've seen what happens when I don't keep an eye on you.
让我和他说说话
Let me talk to him.
他才21个月  不会用电话
He's 21 months old. He doesn't use the phone.
我说就行
I'll do all the talking.
只是想让他听听我的声音
I just want him to hear my voice.
-我想他  -我知道
-I miss him.  -I know.
我回头打给你  好吗?
Let me call you back, okay?
现在不方便
This isn't a good time.
-我们走吧  -嘘 是Michael
-We gotta go.  -Shh..it's Michael.
那是谁啊?
Who's that?
明天再谈  好吗?  我上班时候打给你
Let's talk tomorrow,okay? I'll call you from work.
到底怎么回事
What the hell is going on?
Michael  听我说
Michael, listen.
我一直在和别人约会
I've been seeing someone.
什么?
What?
是谁
Who?
-知道有什么用呢  -是谁?
-Does it make any difference?  -Who is it?
Brian Porter
聘用你的那个人
The guy who hired you.
-不是你想的那样  -那你说你需要时间来考虑
-It wasn't like that before.  -So when you said you needed time to think...
你我之间的时候,你是在说谎了?
about us, you were just lying.?
-不是  我确实是  然后我... -我去阿姆斯特丹
-No, I did, and I realized... -I'm coming to Amsterdam.
Michael  别来  我们之间结束了
Michael, don't. It's over between us.
我不是去找你  我去找Walt
I'm not coming for you.I'm coming for Walt.
我要把我儿子带回来
I'm getting my son back.
快叫救护车! 救救他!
Call an ambulance!  Help him!
Charlie?
这些是Claire的东西  谁放到这儿的
These are Claire's things. Who brought them here?
是我  怎么了  你在干什么
I did. Why? What are you doing?
找不到了  去哪儿了呢
I can't find it. I don't know where it is.
什么?
What?
Claire的日记
Claire's diary
她把她的日记放到边袋里  我知道因为我看见过她放那
She kept her diary in this side pocket.I know because I saw her put it there.
有人拿走了
Someone's taken it.
再问一次  我们在找什么
What are we looking for again?
长金属棒或塑料管
Any long piece of metal or plastic tubing.
任何能当作...
Anything that looks like...
框架的东西
it'd work as a frame.
拿框架干什么
A frame for what?
你很快就会知道的
You'll see soon enough.
嘿  把坐垫  塑料  油布归类
Hey,separate the cushions, the plastic, the tarp.
把你找到的东西都分类摆放  那样容易区分
Put everything you find in different piles so we can take stock.
是在惩罚我吗?
Am I being punished?
什么  和你老头子在一起干活就是惩罚你吗?
What You think working with your old man is punishment?
不是的  小子
No man
是我们在掌控自己命运
It's just us taking control of our destiny.
感觉是在惩罚我
Feels like punishment.
Sawyer...
嘿  Sawyer
Hey Sawyer
其实,我可以直接进去
You know, I could just go inside.
敬酒还是罚酒
Trick or treat.
你二人今天要卖些什么呢?
So, what are you two selling today?
Claire的日记在哪儿
Where's Claire's diary?
有人从她包里拿走了
Someone took it from her bag.
噢  我懂了
Oh, I get it.
东西一丢
Something goes missing
你立刻就会想到是我拿的
and right away you figure it's gotta be me that took it.
你到底拿没拿那日记?
Do you have the diary or not?
说的是这个吗?
You mean this one?
给我
Give it to me.
我看不好吧
I'm not sure that's the best idea.
或许Claire小姐们儿不乐意让你看呢
Maybe Missy Claire don't want you reading it.
我没想要看
I wasn't gonna read it.
你就不好奇她怎么描述你的吗?
You're not curious what she wrote about you?
你个混蛋  你看了吗?
You bastard. Did you read it?
这附近好的文学作品不多
Good literature's kinda scarce around here.
他看了!
He read it!
给我们吧
Just give it to us.
"亲爱的日记  我被过气的...
"Dear Diary, I'm getting really freaked out by that has-been...
流行天王吓坏了
pop star
我想他在跟踪我"
I think he's stalking me"
Sawyer!
"日记  英国的小矮子还是弃而不舍"
"Diary, the little limey runt just won't let up."
你打的象个娘们儿
You hit like a ponce.
-噢  是吗?  -好了  够了
-Oh, yeah?  -All right, enough.
你其实没看过  是吧
You didn't really read it, did you?
只是还没来得及看
I just hadn't gotten around to it yet.
我去拿些水
I'm gonna get some water.
恩  好
Yeah, okay.
给我带些
Would you bring me some?
好吗
Please?
好吗  谢谢
Please and thank you.
我还真得多练练
You gotta work on that.
Boone
你们还要继续空手而归吗?
So you guys are just gonna keep coming back without any food?
嘿  我说正经的呐
Hey, I'm serious.
你怎么了  Boone
What's going on with you,Boone?
你好怪异啊
Could you be acting any weirder?
Shannon
你自从初中就得了贪食症
You've been a functioning bulimic since junior high.
我想如果能减一两个尺码你会很激动吧
I thought you'd be excited about dropping a size or two.
既然你总是空手而归
Well,since you're not having any luck with the hunting,
也许你该去帮一下Michael
maybe you should help Michael.
他在造木筏
He's building a raft.
我还想去帮他呢
I was thinking I would help him out.
也许最后会从这儿出去
maybe finally get the hell outta here.
你帮我好吗?
Why don't you help me?
不  谢了
No, thanks.
你父亲不愿意让我们在一起
Your father doesn't want us spending time together.
他又不是我老大
He's not the boss of me.
可他是你父亲
But he's your father.
并且他关心你  你要尊重他
And he cares about you,and you need to show him respect.
我是说真的  Walt
I'm serious, Walt.
你别再来找我了
You're not to come to me anymore.
该死!
Damn it!
你怎么回事?
What is wrong with you?
-我刚要去看...  -我告诉过你离我儿子远点儿!
-I was just coming to see...  -I told you to stay away from my son!
-不是他,我只是...  -Walt  我不想听你解释
-He didn't.I was just...  -Walt I don't want to hear it from you!
我只是让他把这铅笔带给你
I was giving him this pencil to give to you.
我想你会用得着
I thought you could use it.
把它当作是...
Consider it...
友好的赠品
a peace offering.
我要是再看到你和我儿子在一起
I catch you with my son again
我就干掉你
I'll kill you.
你个混蛋
You're a jerk.
你说我什么?
What did you say to me?
Locke没做错什么  他是我的朋友!
Mr Locke didn't do anything. He's my friend!
现在不是了
He's not anymore.
是我在照顾你
I'm looking out for you.
你才不关心我  你从未关心过我
You don't care about me. You never cared about me.
-什么?  -你只是在我妈死后才出现了
-What?  -You only showed up after Mom died.
我小时候你到哪儿去了  没影了吧
Where were you when I was growing up,huh? Nowhere!
听着  Walt  这一言难尽
Listen, Walt. It's complicated.
我才不管  你不是我父亲
I don't even care! You're not my father!
你要恨我吗?
You wanna hate me?
你要因为一些我无法改变的事来惩罚我吗?  好
You gonna punish me for something I can't change? Fine.
但你还是要听我话
But you will listen to me.
你现在给我到那边去
Now, you get over there,
就在那呆着
and you stay there.
快!
Now!
真不错呢
That's really wonderful.
噢  多谢
Oh, thanks.
给我儿子的
For my son.
他下周就要两岁了
He's gonna be two next week.
是吗  我还不知道你有个孩子
Yeah? I didn't know you have a kid.
有的
Yeah.
恩  呃
Yeah.Um
他和他妈住在阿姆斯特丹
He lives in Amsterdam with his mom.
去看过他吗
Ever gonna visit him?
没有
No
还没看过
not yet.
我与小轿车来了个拥抱
I had a little, you know,run-in with a car.
不知道该写些什么
I never know what to write.
笑话怎么样
How about a joke?
不知道
I don't know.
哪类笑话
What kinda joke?
"什么东西有黑色  白色和红色呢"
How about "What's black, white and red all over?"
恩  报纸  对吧
Yeah, a newspaper, right?
被太阳晒伤的企鹅
A penguin with a sunburn.
-好傻哦  -相信我  我是四个孩子的妈
-That's really dumb  -Trust me.Mother of four talking here.
他会很开心的
He'll get a kick out of it.
你好  Michael
Hello, Michael.
Susan
我最后还是给Andy打电话了
Finally called Andy
因为两个多月没有你的音信
when I hadn't heard from you in over two months.
我还是从他那知道你发生了意外  你该给我打电话
I had to hear about your accident from him. You should've called me.
恩
Yeah
考虑到我们最后一次谈话的情况...
well, considering how our last conversation went...
我真的很抱歉
I'm so sorry about that.
你带Walt来了吗?
Hey, did you bring Walt?
没带  他在家
No.No. He's at home.
在家  和Brian在一起?
Home.With Brian?
那你来这干什么
So, what are you doing here, anyway?
来看你
I came to see you.
我看起来相当不错  是吧
So, I look pretty good, huh?
没那么糟糕
Not that bad.
护士说你能够完全康复
The nurses say you're expected to make a full recovery.
恩  要进行一年的理疗
Yeah, after a year of physical therapy.
一年
A year.
-我会替你付所有的医疗费用  -什么
-I'm covering all your medical costs.  -What?
我和医院管理部门说过了
I've already spoken to the hospital administrator,
你的帐单都由我来付
And all your bills are coming directly toward me.
怎么回事
What is this about?
Brian和我要结婚了
Brian and I are getting married.
多好啊...
How nice for...
你什么都不必说  听着就行
You don't have to say anything. Just listen.
我们月底将搬到意大利
We're moving to Italy at the end of the month.
Brian将接管公司在罗马的办公室
Brian's taking over the firm's Rome offices.
听起来Brian万事顺心呐
Sounds like Brian's on a roll.
并且他想要领养Walt
And he wants to adopt Walt.
我知道很难受
Look, I know this is hard.
但就考虑一下
But just think about it.
你跟我开玩笑  是吗?
You're kidding me, right?
想想怎么做才对Walt好
Consider what's best for Walt.
你可以一直坚持自己的立场 但自问一下...
You can keep holding on if you want.But ask yourself...
为什么要这么做  是真的为了他?
why you're doing that. Is it really for him?
还是为了你自己?
Or is it for you?
嘿 老兄
Uh, dude
你孩子不见了
your kid's gone.
什么?
What?
他牵着狗走了
He just grabbed the dog and took off.
我知道他去哪儿了
I know where he's gone.
Locke
他到底在哪儿?
Where the hell is he?
-什么  -我没心情和你捉迷藏  Walt在哪儿?
-What  -I'm not in the mood for your games, man. Where's Walt?
-Walt不在这里  Michael  -别骗我
-Walt's not here, Michael  -Don't lie to me.
老兄  他不在这  看看周围
Hey man, he is not here. Look around.
我没和你说话
Hey, I'm not talking to you.
今早我告诉他别来找我了
I told him this morning that he couldn't be around me anymore.
我在试着尊重你的意愿
I'm trying to respect your wishes.
那如果他没有...
Well, then if he's not...
咱们走  去找你孩子吧
Let's go find your boy.
谢谢...
Thanks...
其实不用你帮我
You really didn't have to help, you know.
我能行
I could've managed.
我打架也不是第一次了
I've had my share of manly encounters.
我只是看你需要个同伴
I just thought you could use the company.
你还好吧
You okay?
恩
Yeah.
怪事
It's weird.
我以前都不怎么了解她...现在也不怎么了解她
I barely knew her...Barely know her
Claire
她失踪一周了
She's been missing over a week, and...
没有她的每一天  感觉自己就象...
every day she's gone, it feels like...
支离破碎...
bits of me are crumbling...
或是什么的
or something.
你应该保护好她的东西
I think it's right that you should keep her stuff safe...
直到她会回来
till she gets back.
恩
Yeah.
来  Vincent
Come on, Vincent.
Vincent  别乱动
Vincent! Cut it out!
别乱动  Vincent  怎么了?
Cut it out! Vincent What's wrong?
Vincent
你该看看他是如何设法逃避责任的
You should have seen him trying to weasel his way out.
不遗余力地推延案子进展
Anything not to let the case go forward.
-他说不是他司法管辖范围  -你跟我开玩笑是吧
He was arguing it wasn't his jurisdiction.  -Oh, you're kidding me.
我倒想呢  连续三次同样的论据
I wish I was. Same argument third time in a row.
Barkley说是移民问题
Barkley said it was an immigration issue.
Barkley  老样子
Barkley. That's classic.
他以为我刚接触到澳大利亚的法律  我就是乡巴佬什么的
He thinks 'cause I'm new to Australian law that I'm some kind of yokel or something.
嘿...干嘛呐?
Hey. Hello?
做作业
Homework.
我说过我需要帮助
I told you I need help.
他需要帮助
He needs help.
我是律师  甜心  我能分辨出谁在偷懒
I'm a lawyer,sweetheart. I can tell when someone's stalling.
谁在乎澳大利亚的鸟儿?
Who cares about birds of Australia?
我们在澳大利亚
We're in Australia.
没事吧
You okay?
我觉得有点...感冒了
I think I'm feeling kind of...flu-ey.
-难道我们不该研究埃及的鸟之类的吗  -你最近没睡多少觉
-Shouldn't we study birds of Egypt or somthing?  -You haven't been sleeping much lately.
也许你该请一天假
Maybe you need to take a personal day.
我选了青铜杜鹃
I picked the bronze-cuckoo.
-有意思  你想看看吗?  -那Barkley呢?
-It's funny, you wanna see?  -What about Barkley?
我是说看起来没意思  只是因为那名字
I mean, it doesn't look funny. Just the name.
-睡懒觉? 那是奢望  -Brian  看  看
-Sleeping in late? That's too much of a fantasy  -Hey Brain look! look!
你没在看啊
You're not looking!
噢  天那!
Oh, my God!
它死了吗?
Is it dead?
恩
Yeah.
可怜的家伙
Poor guy.
Vincent
Michael Dawson?
恩  有何贵干?
Yeah. Can I help you?
我是Brian Porter
I'm Brian Porter.
Susan的Brian吗
Susan's Brian?
是的 能进来吗?
Yeah.Can I come in?
我要和你谈谈
I need to talk to you.
Susan知道你来这吗  老兄
Susan know you're here, man?
Susan昨天死了
Susan died yesterday.
拜托
Please
她  呃...
She, uh...
她得的是血液病
It turns out she had a blood disorder.
发病只有一周时间
She was only sick for about a week.
我不知...我  呃...
I didn't know...I uh...
我和她有段时间没说话了
I hadn't talked to her in a while...
坐
Sit down.
呃  那Walt呢?
Uh...and Walt?
-他怎么样  呃...?  -挺好的  他  呃...
-How is he, uh...?  -Yeah, he's fine.He is,uh...
他和他保姆在家
He's back home with his nanny.
什么?
What?
我是说他没事
I mean he's fine
我是说,考虑到...你也知道的
I mean, considering...You know.
他刚失去母亲你就把他丢在家里吗?
You left him home after he just lost his mother?
在她死之前
Before she died,
Susan...
她告诉我她想让你作Walt的监护人
she told me she wanted you to have custody of Walt.
她什么
She what?
恩  我想她只是认为...
Well, I think she just thought...
我是说  因为你是他的父亲
I mean, since you're his father...
我已经有九年没当他的父亲了
I haven't been his father in nine years.
恩
Yeah, well,
你瞧说的就是这事...
that's kinda the thing, see...
听着  我深爱Susan
Look, I loved Susan very much.
我从开始就对她开门见山
And I was honest with her from the beginning,
可她...她不听
but she...she wouldn't hear it.
听什么?
Hear what?
我...我不想当父亲  知道吗?
That I...I didn't want to be a father, all right?
我就是不知道如何去当父亲
I just don't know how.
你到底在说什么啊  老兄?  你领养了他
What the hell are you talking about,man? You adopted him.
对  对  我是领养了他. 因为她想要那样
Yes,yes,I did.because she wanted that,
而我想要她
and I wanted her
听我说...
Look...
这是两张机票...一张往返
Theses are two tickets...one round-trip
一张单程从悉尼到纽约
the other one-way, Sydney to New York.
信封里有旅行的费用
The envelope has money in it for travel expenses.
她没告诉你...
She didn't tell you...
她想让我来当监护人  这是你的主意
she wanted me to have custody of him. This is your idea.
我现在快崩溃了  知道吗?
I'm a wreck right now, okay?
那我该体谅你吗?
I'm supposed to give a damn about you?
我刚失去了我爱的女人  我没法当他的父亲
Hey I just lost the woman I love.And I can't be his father.
-他不是我儿子  -你个婊子养的  你说什么呐?
-He is not my son  -You son of a bitch! What are you talking about?
-他只知道你这么一个父亲!  -不光是这样
-You're the only father he knows!  -It's more than that.
-好吧,那是什么?  -他有些不对劲
-Well,then,waht?  -There's something about him.
你到底在说什么  老兄?
What the hell are you talking about,man?
有时候有他在
Sometimes when he's around
就会有事发生
things happen.
不知为何  他与众不同
He's different somehow.
在这里!
Over here!
-到底怎么...  -救命啊
-What the hell would...  -Help, please! Help!
-Walt?  -这边
-Walt?  -This way.
Walt
Walt随时会从学校回来
Walt should be home from school any minute.
Porter先生让我把这个交给你
Mr. Porter asked me to give you that.
一些Susan的遗物
Some of Susan's effects.
噢  好  谢谢
Oh,okay,thanks.
还有些别的东西
There's something else.
是什么?
What's that?
我认为Walt应该得到的东西
Something I think Walt should have.
失陪
Excuse me.
Walt
-恩  -有人来看你了
-Yeah?  -There's somebody here to see you.
爸!  救命!
Dad! Help!
-爸!  -Walt!
-Dad!  -Walt!
爸  救我! 快!
Dad, help! Please!
-救命  -嘿  Walt...
-Help!  -Hey, Walt...
嘘  嘘  嘘
Shh,Shh,Shh
爸!
Dad!
来!  爬上去!
Come on! Up here!
Michael
爸
Dad
嘿  Walt
Hey, Walt.
你是谁
Who are you?
我  呃...
I'm, uh...
我是你父亲
I'm your father.
你要知道...
I want you to know...
听我说  我无法解释对你母亲的事...
Listen, I can't explain how sorry I am...
我有多抱歉
about your mom.
你要知道我们  呃...
You should know that we, uh...
我们有你的时候我们很恩爱
we loved each other very much when we had you.
Brian在哪儿?
Where's Brian?
Brian不在这儿
Brian's not here.
我是来接你回家的
I come to bring you home with me.
我不会和你走
I'm not going anywhere with you.
Walt  我能...?
Walt, can I...?
呃...我知道
Uh...I know
真的很难理解...这所有的事
this is really hard to understand...all of this.
知道吗  Brian...
See, Brian...
Brian非常爱你
Brian loves you very much.
他想让你和他在一起 但不是他能决定的
And he wants you to stay with him, but it's not his choice.
是我决定的
It's mine.
我是你的合法监护人
I'm your legal guardian.
并且  呃
And, uh
不是说他会从此消失
it's not like he's gonna disappear from your life.
他还会打电话给你  写信给你
He'll still call you, write to you,
有时间就来看你
come to see you whenever he can.
还有你知道吗
And you know
你可以继续带着你的狗
you'll still have your dog.
可Vincent不是我的
But Vincent isn't mine.
是Brian的
He's Brian's.
Brian说它是你的了
Brian said you could have him.
爸
Dad.
-嘿  Walt!  -爸
-Hey, Walt!  -Dad!
-爸!  -你在哪儿  爸?
-Dad!  -Where are you, Dad?
坚持住
Hang on
好  我们走  走
Okay. Let's go. Let's go.
Walt  在那别动  知道吗
Hey Walt, just hang in there, okay?
我来了  小子
I'm coming, man.
-爸!  -Walt!
-Dad!  -Walt!
把刀丢给他
Throw him the knife.
Walt
他要是靠近了  就用刀!
If he comes near you, use it!
在那别动  小子!
Stay there, buddy!
来
Come here.
爸
Dad
-你没事吧?  -恩
-You okay?  -Yeah.
-Are you okay?  -Yeah.
好  无论如何
All right.Whatever you do
你都紧紧抓住这个  知道吗  紧紧抓住
you hold onto this tight. You got me? Tight
-那你呢  -别管我
-What about you?  -Don't worry about me.
我马上就来  好吗?
I'll be right behind you, okay?
好,抓住了
So, hold on.
好了  Locke  快!
Okay, Locke, now!
拉
Pull
拉  Locke  拉
Pull him. Locke Pull
过来
Come here.
对不起  对不起
I'm sorry. I'm sorry
不  不  不
No No No
没关系
It's okay
我不会说你
We're okay.
你安全了就好
I'm just glad you're safe.
可Vincent,他又跑开了
But Vincent, he ran off again.
他回来...
He found his way...
找到过你一次  Walt
back to you once, Walt.
他还会回来的
He will again.
我有份礼物要送给你
I got a present for you.
你说你喜欢看图片
Since you like to look at pictures.
-这是什么  -打开看看
-What's this?  -Well...
过去八年我寄给你的每封信 每张卡片
Every card, every letter I sent you over the last eight years.
你给我写信了?
You wrote me?
我从没见过
I never saw these.
我妈知道吗?
Did my mom have these?
为什么她不给我呢?
Why didn't she give 'em to me?
不知道
I don't know
可她也没有扔掉  也就是说...
But she didn't throw 'em away either,which means,you know...
她内心深处还是想让你看到的
somewhere inside,she wanted you to have them.
那  这些是你画的喽?
So, you drew these?
为你画的
Just for you.
这个
This one
你两岁生日时我给你画的
I did for your second birthday.
被晒伤的...企鹅?
A penguin... with a sunburn?
-好傻哦  -恩  我知道  我也是那么说的
-That's dumb.  -Yeah, I know.That's what I said.
Jack
Sayid
你得听听这个
You have to hear this.
是什么?
What is that?
是Claire的...她的日记
It's Claire's, her diary.
-你看人家日记吗  -恩  我知道
-You're reading her diary?  -Yeah, I know, I'm bloody scum.
我是他妈的人渣  听听这段
I'm bloody scum. Just listen to this.
"我又做了那个诡异的梦  无法从那黑岩挣脱的梦
"I had that weird dream again, the one with the black rock I can't get away from.
我尝试着要离开  可它不让"
I try to leave it, but it won't let me."
黑岩?
Black rock?
只是梦而已  Charlie
They're just dreams. Charlie
不  Sayid先前提到过黑岩
No. Sayid mentioned the black rock before.
那法国女人说过关于她的队伍从黑岩回来的事
The Frenchwoman said her team was returning from the black rock.
地图上的三角形
The triangle on the map.
也许是地图上的三角形
Maybe it's the triangle on the map.
也许Claire被劫到那去了
Maybe it's where Claire was taken.
-也许她在那里  -也许吧
-Maybe she's there  -Maybe
Charlie  我们都想找到Claire
Charlie  we all want to find Claire.
但半夜去那森林里...
But there's no sense...
是不理智的
going out into the jungle in the middle of the night.
我看那口哨没用  John
I don't think that whistle's working, John.
你不是什么都听得见  Boone
You can't hear everything, Boone.
你应该早点认识到这点
The sooner you learn that, the better.
这我听见了
Well, I heard that.
Vincent
Vincent  是你吗?
Vincent, is that you?
Vincent
Claire
==============|  YYeTs字幕组招募启示  |==============
英文字幕录制(居住在加拿大和美国)  双语字幕校正   时间轴调整
英语翻译   欧美影视新闻翻译  影视评论  论坛版主  美工人员
服务器提供者  发布宣传  联系地址：www.YYeTs.com
==== YYeTs属于网络爱好者组织 加入者仅凭个人兴趣爱好 无报酬 ====